A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia Records, 1961-2001
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia Records, 1961-2001
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1997-016
21.0 cu. ft. 15 boxes
The League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia, records, is composed of correspondence, chapter and national league literature and publications, bulletins, candidate questionnaires, meeting minutes and agendas, budget and financial information, bank statements, returned checks, and treasurer's reports.
League of Women Voters. Montgomery County (Va.).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Initials materials from the League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia Records were donated to Special Collections in September 1997. Additional materials were donated between 1998 and 2002 and in 2003/2004.
Historical Information
The National League of Women Voters was established in 1920, as women in the United States were granted the right to vote, to educate women on how best to exercise their new political rights and responsibilities. Although the programs and priorities have changed over the years, the league is still committed to the following basic purposes: to foster citizen involvement and develop citizen leaders, to help people understand public issues and how government works, to promote discussion of government policies, and to influence public policy.
The League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia, was established on March 28, 1974, with its purpose to promote political responsibility through informed and active participation of citizens in government. Their policy is that they do not support or oppose any political party or candidate, but to take positions on certain issues and support or oppose legislative measures. Any person is eligible for membership who subscribes to the purpose and policy of the league. Voter services include providing information on registration and voting, giving public forums to present candidates, and supplying candidate questionnaire information for news organizations.
Scope and Content
The League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia, records, is composed of correspondence, chapter and national league literature and publications, bulletins, candidate questionnaires, meeting minutes and agendas, budget and financial information, bank statements, returned checks, and treasurer's reports. Topics covered in the records include the Equal Rights Amendment, women in the workforce, natural resources, poverty in Montgomery County, education, and recycling. The records span between 1961 and 2001, which the majority between 1968 and 1988.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged chronologically. Undated materials are at the end.
Adjumct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Mary Fessler Papers, c.1940-2001 (Bulk 1967-1984). Ms2001-012. Finding aid available on the Virginia Heritage database.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
League of Women Voters. Montgomery County (Va.).
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; Montgomery County (Va.)
Contents List
- Land use, 1961-1976 (Box-folder 1-1)
- Community Survey and Data required for organizational meeting in September 1971, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 1-2)
- Member's Handbook, 1966-1989 (Box-folder 1-3)
- By Laws LWV of Montgomery County, 1966-1988 (Box-folder 1-4)
- HR employment, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 1-5)
- Blacksburg Charter study, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 1-6)
- Voter Service, publications, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 1-7)
- Environment quality, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 1-8)
- Intergovernmental relations state item, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 1-9)
- National publications, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 1-10)
- Correspondence--National, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 1-11)
- Foreign policy, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 1-12)
- LWV International Relations; Trade, Panama, 1969-1985 (Box-folder 1-13)
- Finance national helps, 1969-1980 (Box-folder 1-14)
- Mental health, 1970 (Box-folder 1-15)
- State and National By Laws, 1970 (Box-folder 1-16)
- Know Your Country study, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 1-17)
- Welfare, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 1-18)
- Education, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 1-19)
- Housing, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 1-20)
- State Government, Constitution, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 1-21)
- Representative government, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 1-22)
- Equal Rights Amendment, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 1-23)
- Voter education, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 1-24)
- Finance tools, invoice forms and receipts, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 1-25)
- State League publications, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 1-26)
- Divorce and separation, Montgomery County, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 2-1)
- Election laws, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 2-2)
- Fiscal policy, 1970-1984 (Box-folder 2-3)
- LWV bulletins, 1971 (Box-folder 2-4)
- Constitution of Virginia, 1971 (Box-folder 2-5)
- Finance education fund, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2-6)
- Thank you letters on behalf of LWVMC board member, 1971 (Box-folder 2-7)
- Reports of community interviews, 1971 (Box-folder 2-8)
- State Board report, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 2-9)
- Letters on miscellaneous topics, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 2-10)
- US Congress Study and Committee Guide; other information about voting, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 2-11)
- Welfare and human resources, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 2-12)
- Congress, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 2-13)
- Budget for LWV of Montgomery County, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 2-14)
- Publications file, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 2-15)
- Lobbying LWV of Montgomery County, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 2-16)
- Publications, Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 2-17)
- Citizen information, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 2-18)
- Annual report LWV of Montgomery, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 2-19)
- State convention and council, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 2-20 to 2-21 (2 folders))
- Finance drive, 1972 (Box-folder 2-22)
- Finance drive and solicitors kits, 1972 (Box-folder 2-23)
- LWV bulletins, 1972 (Box-folder 2-24)
- US Congress information, 1972 (Box-folder 2-25)
- Voting rights, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2-26)
- Voter service, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2-27)
- Election Laws information, bills, observing forms, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2-28)
- Correspondence--Local, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2-29)
- Day Care, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2-30)
- Election laws, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2-31)
- Finances, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2-32)
- State and national board, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2-33)
- Inter League organization, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2-34)
- William Wampler congressional interviews, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2-35)
- Swap shop ideas, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 2-36)
- Legislative state, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 2-37)
- Registration information, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 3-1)
- Candidate questionnaires, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-2)
- County Government--Local study and budget, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-3)
- Poll observing, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-4)
- Treasurer, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-5)
- Voters of Virginia, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-6)
- State budget, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-7)
- Freedom of information, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3-8)
- Election day telephone answering information service, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 3-9)
- Finance budgets, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 3-10)
- State council, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 3-11)
- Candidates questionnaires--Congressional, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 3-12)
- Voter services, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 3-13)
- Information on juvenile related topics; court, houses, jail, correctional facilities, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 3-14)
- Candidates questionnaires, town council, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 3-15)
- Equal Rights Amendment publications, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 3-16)
- Information from The National Association on Volunteers in Criminal Justice; newspaper clippings, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 3-17)
- Membership, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 3-18)
- Provisional Chapter history, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 3-19)
- Voter service, pamphlets, publications, memos, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 3-20)
- School information, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 3-21)
- National budgets, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 3-22 to 3-23 (2 folders))
- LWV bulletins, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 3-24)
- Pamphlets on Education Fund, pick a candidate and facts, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 4-1)
- National convention, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 4-2 to 4-3 (2 folders)
- Indians, 1973 (Box-folder 4-4)
- LWV bulletins, 1973 (Box-folder 4-5)
- Nonprofit status, 1973 (Box-folder 4-6)
- Candidates questionnaires, 6th Legislative District, 1973 (Box-folder 4-7)
- LWV newsletter, 1973 (Box-folder 4-8)
- Copy of "Know Your County," 1973 (Box-folder 14-18)
- Legislative news, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 4-9)
- State workshop, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 4-10)
- Human resources, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 4-11)
- Juvenile justice, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 4-12)
- Finance annual reports, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 4-13)
- Publications--Information from state, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 4-14)
- Virginia election laws, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 4-15)
- Candidates questionnaires, House of Delegates, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 4-16)
- Bulletins from other leagues, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 4-17)
- Finance Drive letters, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 4-18)
- State voters service election guides, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 4-19)
- State government league action, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 4-20)
- Program Planning, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 4-21)
- Consensus, 1974 (Box-folder 4-22)
- LWV bulletin, 1974 (Box-folder 4-23)
- Corrections and related laws handbook, 1974 (Box-folder 4-24)
- LWV phone directory, 1974 (Box-folder 4-25)
- Charter, 1974 (Box-folder 4-26)
- Health status goals, 1974 (Box-folder 4-27)
- Finance drive, 1974 (Box-folder 4-28)
- Local contacts, 1974 (Box-folder 4-29)
- Membership Lists, 1974 (Box-folder 4-30)
- Candidate questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4-31)
- New River, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4-32)
- Government Forms & Charter for Blacksburg, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14-17)
- Political accountability, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4-33)
- Election education, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 4-34)
- Local publications, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 4-35)
- State Board reports, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 4-36)
- Candidates Forum--Town Council, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 5-1)
- Census and population shifts for Montgomery County, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 5-2)
- Finance, state help, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 5-3)
- Finance ideas and projects, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 5-4)
- Bulletin sponsors, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 5-5)
- Pamphlets and information on "Writing Your Representatives", "Reassessment", and "Voting, Taxes and Services in Montgomery Co.," 1974-1983 (Box-folder 5-6)
- National Programs for Action Government, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 5-7)
- Local Action, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 5-8)
- Membership, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 5-9)
- VA state finances, shares of revenue, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 5-10)
- Membership, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 5-11)
- Newspaper clippings of Blue Ridge projects, 1974 (Box-folder 5-12)
- Finance self study, 1975 (Box-folder 5-13)
- Membership roster and pamphlets with information about the LWV, 1975 (Box-folder 5-14)
- LWV state level legal lies; pres. briefings, 1975 (Box-folder 5-15)
- LWV Presidency of US, 1975 (Box-folder 5-16)
- Human resources, 1975 (Box-folder 5-17)
- Bulletin, 1975 (Box-folder 5-18)
- Finance drive, 1975 (Box-folder 5-19)
- LWV calendar and other information, 1975 (Box-folder 5-20)
- Public Relations How-to's, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5-21)
- Local issues update, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5-22)
- Grants, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5-23)
- League Principles/Action, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14-16)
- Program/Action, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14-15)
- Newspaper clippings, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 5-24)
- State correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 5-25)
- Action letters and statements--Local, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 5-26)
- Welfare budget and study, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 5-27)
- Litigation, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 5-28)
- Montgomery County Emergency Assistance Program Inc., 1975-1984 (Box-folder 5-29)
- Publicity releases, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 5-30)
- Women's Right's, VA--literature and legislature for TALK, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 5-31)
- Miscellaneous, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 5-32)
- Scrapbook items, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 5-33)
- Montgomery County League publications, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 5-34)
- Finance drive, 1976 (Box-folder 6-1)
- Pertinent Congressional Record, 1976 (Box-folder 6-2)
- Public Meeting--City status for Blacksburg, 1976 (Box-folder 6-3)
- Bulletin, 1976 (Box-folder 6-4)
- Candidates for election, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6-5)
- Land use issues/ problems, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6-6)
- Expenses, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6-7)
- Voters service, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6-8)
- Legislators potluck lobbying, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6-9)
- Budget committee, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6-10)
- Nominating committee, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6-11)
- Board issues, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6-12)
- United nations, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6-13)
- Member interest forms, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6-14)
- General LWV correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6-15)
- Finance Advisory Committee, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 6-16)
- General elections--November, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 6-17)
- Secretary Board meeting, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 6-18)
- Finance Drive correspondence--General, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 6-19)
- Daily calendar, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 6-20)
- Volunteers for various projects, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 6-21)
- State Water Control Board, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 6-22)
- Publicity, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 6-23)
- Program coordinator, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 6-24)
- Local, public relations, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 6-25)
- Nonpartisan Policy, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 6-26)
- National Lobbying Statements, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 6-27)
- Local Publications, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 6-28)
- Local Handbook, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 6-29)
- Public meeting, Justice for Juveniles--New River Valley, 1977 (Box-folder 6-30)
- Bulletin, 1977 (Box-folder 6-31)
- Finance drive, 1977 (Box-folder 6-32)
- LWV Calendar and other Information, 1977 (Box-folder 6-33)
- History of Virginia State, 1977 (Box-folder 6-34)
- LWV Action and General, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 6-35)
- Finance drive planning and procedures, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 6-36)
- Poll observer forms, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 6-37)
- Miscellaneous information, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 6-38)
- State programs--Women's Rights, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 6-39)
- Local Budget, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 6-40)
- Annual meeting, agendas, minutes, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 6-41)
- LWV bulletins, 1978 (Box-folder 7-1)
- Finance public relations, 1978 (Box-folder 7-2)
- Finance drive, 1978 (Box-folder 7-3)
- LWV calendar and other information, 1978 (Box-folder 7-4)
- Public meeting, housing needs--Montgomery County, 1978 (Box-folder 7-5)
- Municipal elections, 1978 (Box-folder 7-6)
- Fundraising pamphlets and information, 1978 (Box-folder 7-7)
- LWV study kits national and state voting, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 7-8)
- Government information pamphlets, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 7-9)
- Financial statements and treasurers report, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 7-10)
- Voters service, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 7-11)
- Local Candidate Questionnaires/election guides, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 7-12)
- Minutes from board meetings, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 7-13)
- Financial information, pamphlets, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 7-14)
- National Board reports, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 7-15)
- State Program for Action Women's Rights and Virginia Laws, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 7-16)
- League principles, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 7-17)
- Various program tapes, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 7-18)
- Virginia legislature directory pamphlets, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 7-19)
- General Election--November, 1979 (Box-folder 7-20)
- Board tools, 1979 (Box-folder 7-21)
- Human Rights Covenants, 1979 (Box-folder 7-22)
- LWV Calendar and other information, 1979 (Box-folder 7-23)
- Women's Right article, 1979 (Box-folder 7-24)
- Reapportionment information pamphlets, 1979 (Box-folder 7-25)
- Juvenile Justice Roster core, 1979 (Box-folder 7-26)
- System of justice, 1979 (Box-folder 7-27)
- LWV bulletins, 1979 (Box-folder 7-28)
- Reapportionment for the Eighties, 1979 (Box-folder 7-29)
- Local Board packet, 1979 (Box-folder 7-30)
- Women's Rights Kit, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 7-31)
- Voter registration, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7-32)
- Finance drive, 1979 (Box-folder 7-33)
- Candidates forum, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 7-34)
- Women's Rights Property, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 7-35)
- League politics/purpose, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 7-36)
- General Election--November, 1980 (Box-folder 7-37)
- LWV calendar and other information, 1980 (Box-folder 7-38)
- Urban Policy Abroad booklet, 1980 (Box-folder 7-39)
- LWV bulletins, 1980 (Box-folder 7-40)
- Comprehensive Plan, Environment Sensitivity Areas, 1980 (Box-folder 7-41)
- Municipal elections, 1980 (Box-folder 7-42)
- Ideas finance education, 1980 (Box-folder 7-43)
- Coastal concerns--Chesapeake Bay, 1980 (Box-folder 7-44)
- LWV of US Principles, Basis for Action, 1980 (Box-folder 8-1)
- LWV of Montgomery County Board, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8-2)
- Information about introducing the LWV of Montgomery County, VA, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8-3)
- Finance drive, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8-4)
- Prospective members, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8-5)
- Get Out the Vote, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 8-6)
- Women's Rights, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 8-7)
- Finance Committee files, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 8-8)
- Miscellaneous information, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 8-9)
- Employment, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 8-10)
- Reports Women in Poverty, Montgomery County, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 8-11)
- Membership report, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 8-12)
- State membership, memos and aids, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 8-13)
- Information pamphlets on the League of Women Voters, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 8-14)
- Brochures, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 14-3)
- General Elections--November, 1981 (Box-folder 8-15)
- Mountain Lake Wilderness Proposal, 1981 (Box-folder 8-16)
- LWV bulletin, 1981 (Box-folder 8-17)
- LWV calendar and other information, 1981 (Box-folder 8-18)
- Education, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8-19)
- Finance drive, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8-20)
- New River Community Action, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8-21)
- Women in Poverty in Montgomery County, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8-22)
- Volunteers Filling the Gap?, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-23)
- Women in Poverty in Montgomery County, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-24)
- Health food, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-25)
- Health statistics, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-26)
- Women in education, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-27)
- Welfare, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-28)
- Children, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8-29)
- Equal Rights--component education, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 8-30)
- Finance information, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 8-31)
- Calendars of events, 1981-1997 (Box-folder 8-32)
- Local finance, 1982 (Box-folder 8-33)
- LWV Calendar and other information, 1982 (Box-folder 8-34)
- LWV Bulletins, 1982 (Box-folder 8-35)
- Information; questionnaire; election guides, calendars, public service announcements, 1982 (Box-folder 9-1)
- Local Program--Forms of Government for Montgomery County, 1982 (Box-folder 9-2)
- ABC Accepting, 1982 (Box-folder 9-3)
- Local Interviews with Legislatures, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-4)
- Local Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-5)
- Women's income, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-6)
- Reagan Cuts, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-7)
- Action Packed Politics, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-8)
- State Program--Water, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-9)
- Finance drive, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-10)
- Treasurers records, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9-11)
- Financing education, VA, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-12)
- Consultant correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-13)
- Workshops, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-14)
- Treasurer's reports, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-15)
- National voters service; memos, pamphlets, aids, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-16)
- State Board reports, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-17)
- Local correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9-18)
- Local Board meeting minutes, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-19)
- Local Board meeting agendas, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-20)
- Local calendar, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-21)
- Working women, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-22)
- National conventions councils, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-23)
- National correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-24)
- State Times for Action, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-25)
- State Program--general information and positions, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-26)
- Hazardous work, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 9-27)
- National resource water, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 9-28)
- Voting information, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 9-29)
- National board list and By-Laws, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 9-30)
- Sewage handling and disposal, 1983 (Box-folder 9-31)
- LWV bulletins, 1983 (Box-folder 9-32)
- LWV calendar and other information, 1983 (Box-folder 9-33)
- Legislative interviews, 1983 (Box-folder 9-34)
- Self study, 1983 (Box-folder 9-35)
- National resources uranium mining, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9-36)
- State--public relations, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9-37)
- Treasurers record, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9-38)
- National Money Matters: finance, treasurer's reports, memos, aids, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9-39)
- State Program for Action Systems of Justice, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9-40)
- State correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9-41)
- National program for study National Security, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9-42)
- State Legislature: directories, letters and procedures, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9-43)
- State Convention and Council, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9-44)
- State Program--Reapportionment/Redistributing, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9-45)
- Local voters service, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9-46)
- Coalition Guidelines, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 9-47)
- State finance, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 9-48)
- National Membership: memos, aids, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 10-1)
- Forum information, Stop Watch, time cards, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 10-2)
- State Legislative Newsletter, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 10-3)
- Pamphlets describing the LWV, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 10-4)
- State Legislative Newsletters, 1984 (Box-folder 10-5)
- LWV bulletins, 1984 (Box-folder 10-6)
- Voter service Congressional Debate, 1984 (Box-folder 10-7)
- Copyright, 1984 (Box-folder 10-8)
- IRS Forms, 1984 (Box-folder 10-9)
- Postal Permits, 1984 (Box-folder 10-10)
- Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 10-11)
- Local observer corps, 1984 (Box-folder 10-12)
- Miscellaneous information, 1984 (Box-folder 10-13)
- Copies, bills, checks, receipts, deposit slips, 1984 (Box-folder 10-14)
- Women's Studies, Comparable Worth and Pay Equality, 1984 (Box-folder 10-15)
- Crisis Control information, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 10-16)
- Mental health, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 10-17)
- Membership local, 1985 (Box-folder 10-18)
- Registration polling places, election guide, 1985 (Box-folder 10-19)
- LWV bulletins, 1985 (Box-folder 10-20)
- Montgomery County Human Services Commission Quarterly newsletter, 1985 (Box-folder 10-21)
- Miscellaneous information, 1985 (Box-folder 10-22)
- Forums/Debates, 1985 (Box-folder 14-5)
- Texaco Material on the environment, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 10-23)
- Mental health, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 10-24)
- Office log, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 10-25)
- Treasurer's reports, bank statements, phone bill, returned checks, 1985 (Box-folder 10-26)
- Minutes from meetings, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 10-27)
- Program, 1986 (Box-folder 10-28)
- Filling system, 1986 (Box-folder 10-29)
- Children, 1986 (Box-folder 10-30)
- LWV Bulletins, 1986 (Box-folder 10-31)
- State Programs, Mental Health Services in VA, 1986 (Box-folder 10-32)
- Acid Precipitation Digest, 1986 (Box-folder 10-33)
- Zone and planning, 1986 (Box-folder 10-34)
- Child Care, 1986 (Box-folder 10-35)
- Bank statements, bills, deposit slips, returned checks, treasurer report, 1986 (Box-folder 10-36)
- National publications, catalogues and order forms, 1986 (Box-folder 10-37)
- National Voter Magazine, 1986 (Box-folder 10-38)
- League activity information, 1986 (Box-folder 10-39)
- Montgomery County Budget, 1986 (Box-folder 10-40)
- House of Delegates Legislative offices and standing committee, 1986 (Box-folder 10-41)
- National Convention, 1986 (Box-folder 14-9)
- Mental health, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 10-42)